waitrapp.com 2016-11-15

# Privacy Policy | Waitr

**Email Opt Out** Waitr will not ever give away or sell your email address. By joining our mailing list, you are agreeing to receive promotional emails from time to time. We try to make those as relevant as possible to you (new restaurants that deliver to you, popular joints in your neighborhood, etc.), but if you think we’re doing a rotten job, you can unsubscribe at any time. **Return Policy** Customer satisfaction is our top priority. If there are any problems with your food order or an incorrect charge on your credit card, call us at 877-263-1494 or email [support@waitrapp.com](mailto:support@waitrapp.com) to resolve any issues. We’re here 24/7 to help straighten any issues out. Due to banking turn times credits or adjustments can take up to 7–10 days to appear in your bank account. **Privacy Policy** Waitr, Inc. (“Waitr”) collects certain information through its websites located at [www.WaitrApp.com](http://waitr-wp-website-prod.us-west-2.elasticbeanstalk.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/www.waitrapp.com) and related mobile sites and consumer mobile applications, (collectively, “Sites”). Your privacy is important to Waitr and this Privacy Policy lays out Waitr’s policies and procedures surrounding the collection and handling of such information. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, do not use the Sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Sites. It does not apply to any restaurant websites, other third party services linked to Waitr Sites or offline activities related to Waitr services. 

  1. **Information Waitr Collects –  **Waitr may collect the following information from users of our Sites: first name, last name, street address, city, state, zip code, cross streets (optional), phone number, e-mail address, Sites-specific display name, GPS location (mobile), electronic signature and credit card information (Waitr stores only last four digits) (collectively, “Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”). Waitr is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and Waitr does not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. Use of the Sites requires that you register and/or create an account (“Account”) or use the Sites as a guest. In addition to the PII set forth above, Waitr may collect information regarding Account holders’ Waitr orders, gratuity amounts, favorite restaurants, customer service inquiries, service/restaurant reviews, and certain social networking preferences relating to the Sites (e.g. pages or entities you like, recommend or follow).Waitr also collects aggregated information, demographic information and other information that does not reveal your specific identity (“Non-PII”). Non-PII may include information about the device you use to access the Sites, information from referring websites and your engagement with the Sites. Waitr may publish these statistics or share them with third parties without including PII.Waitr uses HTTPS cookies to collect information about you and your activity on the Sites. Waitr uses this information to remember users on the Sites and to enhance users’ experience on the Sites. For example, when users with Waitr Accounts return to the Sites, cookies identify those users and allow the Sites to provide certain user-specific information such as Waitr account information, past orders, favorite restaurants and user restaurant reviews. To learn more about cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://waitr-wp-website-prod.us-west-2.elasticbeanstalk.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/www.allaboutcookies.org). Waitr also works with third parties for the purpose of advertisement delivery on the Sites. The Non-PII collected about your visits to the Sites may be used by third parties in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These third parties may also set cookies to assist with advertisement delivery services. To learn more about opting-out of cookie-targeted advertising on the Sites (sometimes referred to as online behavioral advertising or OBA), visit  [www.AboutAds.info](http://waitr-wp-website-prod.us-west-2.elasticbeanstalk.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/www.aboutads.info). Some browsers allow you to indicate that you would not like your online activities tracked, using “Do Not Track” indicators (“DNT Indicators”), however, we are not obligated to respond to these indicators. Presently, we are not set up to respond to DNT Indicators. This means that while the Sites may track certain latent information about your online activities, the collected information will be used to improve your use of our Site and in ways consistent with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Waitr’s Use Of Collected Information –  **Waitr uses PII to create users’ Waitr Accounts, to communicate with users (directly and through restaurants and delivery drivers) about Waitr services, offer users additional services, assist with Customer service inquiries, offer promotions and special offers, charge for purchases and gratuities made through Waitr and fulfill Waitr orders. Users may opt to allow Waitr to store certain PII used to create users’ Waitr Accounts, including, but not limited to, credit card information (last four digits only). Waitr uses certain stored PII to customize future order processing for you. You may request that Waitr cease storing certain PII at any time, but you might not be able to take advantage of certain customized features. Users may affirmatively opt-out of receiving promotional communications from Waitr by visiting[https://www.WaitrApp.com/legal/#emailOptOut](https://www.waitrapp.com/legal/#emailOptOut) and providing Waitr with their e-mail address via the opt-out link. Waitr may also use PII to enforce Waitr Terms of Use. Waitr does not sell the information it collects through the Sites to third parties. Waitr shares collected PII with restaurants and delivery drivers only to the extent required to fulfill Waitr orders. Waitr also shares collected PII with third-party vendors and service providers with whom Waitr works to provide application programming interfaces (“APIs”) and other functions for the Sites in connection with the delivery of Waitr services only to the extent necessary to provide those APIs and services. Full credit card numbers are transmitted to Waitr’s credit card processor but are not stored by Waitr. Waitr allows certain social media platforms to host plug-ins or widgets on the Sites which may collect certain information about those users who choose to use those plug-ins or widgets. Waitr may also disclose PII to third parties such as attorneys, collection agencies, tribunals or law enforcement authorities pursuant to valid requests in connection with alleged violations of Waitr terms of use and service or other alleged contract violations, infringement or similar harm to persons or property. User generated content posted through the Sites such as service/restaurant reviews and certain social networking preferences (e.g. pages you “Like” or “Follow”) may be viewed by the general public. Accordingly, Waitr cannot ensure the privacy of any PII included in such user generated content. **3\. Waitr’s Protection of PII –  **Waitr uses reasonable security measures equal to or exceeding industry standard to protect PII from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure. Unfortunately, even with these measures, Waitr cannot guarantee the security of PII. By using the Sites, you acknowledge and agree that Waitr makes no such guarantee, and that you use the Sites at your own risk. **4\. Accessing and Correcting Your PII –  **Registered Waitr Account holders can access and change their own PII using the “Change” or “Edit” function on the Waitr mobile app. Account e-mail addresses cannot be deleted. However, an Account may be closed and Waitr will cause the corresponding e-mail address to be scrambled. A user may then open a new Account with a different e-mail address. If you have questions regarding Waitr’s use or collection of your PII, please contact Waitr’s privacy officer at:[accounts@WaitrApp.com](mailto:accounts@WaitrApp.com). **5\. Privacy Policy Amendments –  **Waitr may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version on this page or on a successor page. The new version will become effective on the posting date, which will be listed at the top of the page as of the effective date February 1, 2014. You agree that you will check for new versions of this Privacy Policy. By continuing to access and/or use the Sites following the posting of a new Privacy Policy version, you agree to be bound by the then-current version. If you do not agree to the terms of the new version of the Privacy Policy, you will stop using the Sites. **6\. Contest and Giveaway Rules –  **From time to time Waitr and/or its Restaurant partners may host contests or giveaways for customers. The following rules will govern such contests: Participation is subject to Waitr’s  [Terms of Use](http://waitr-wp-website-prod.us-west-2.elasticbeanstalk.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/terms-agreements "Terms & Agreements") and [Privacy Policy](http://waitr-wp-website-prod.us-west-2.elasticbeanstalk.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/privacy "Privacy"), which are incorporated as part of these Rules. NO PURCHASE OR CONTRIBUTION NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE OR CONTRIBUTION WILL NOT INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED. Customer is responsible for any applicable taxes on prizes? Must be 13 or older and a legal US resident to play. Void where prohibited. How can you participate? What prizes will be given away? That info will be tweeted from [Waitrs’ Twitter account](http://waitr-wp-website-prod.us-west-2.elasticbeanstalk.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/WaitrApp) and or listed on the WaitrApp.com website. If we post a tweet or message or tell you that we – that’s Waitr – are going to choose a contest winner, we’ll be picking the winner(s) from the pool of participants that we feel followed the rules to their best of their ability. For giveaways where prizes are awarded to participants who are the first set number to respond to a Waitr tweet (such as, “First 10 people to…”), we count based on the timestamp associated with – the tweeted responses received. Winners’ names will be announced on Twitter or Facebook. If we choose you as a winner, we may contact you to collect a bit of info from you in order to give you your prize. If we do not get a response from you within 48 hours of our initial reach out, we’ll award the prize we’d set aside for you to the runner up. We also reserve the right to exclude any participant if we deem a username, profile information or any of that person’s tweets to be offensive in any form. By participating in any Waitr contests or giveaways, you give us permission to use your name,Twitter handle or Facebook handle, profile info, and submissions when announcing a winner. What you submit to us becomes our property. Waitr employees (and their family and friends) are not eligible to participate. **MORE LEGALESE:** **BY PARTICIPATING OR ACCEPTING A PRIZE, PARTICIPANTS RELEASE AND AGREE TO HOLD HARMLESS WAITR, INC., CONTEST OR GIVEAWAY PARTNERS, PRIZE SUPPLIERS, TWITTER, FACEBOOK AND THEIR RESPECTIVE PARENTS, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, AND CONTRACTORS FROM ANY AND ALL EXISTING OR FUTURE ACTUAL OR ALLEGED ACTIONS, CLAIMS AND/OR LIABILITIES OF WHATEVER NATURE INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PERSONAL INJURY, BODILY INJURY (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION WRONGFUL DEATH AND DISABILITY), PROPERTY DAMAGE, AND LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY OTHER KIND, ARISING IN WHOLE OR IN PART, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, FROM ACCEPTANCE, POSSESSION, USE OF MISUSE OF THE PRIZE, PARTICIPATION IN THIS, AND/OR PARTICIPATION IN ANY CONTEST OR GIVEAWAY OR PRIZE RELATED ACTIVITIES.** Participants agree to be bound by these Rules and the decisions of Waitr. In the event of fraud, a force majeure event, a technical error or malfunction which, at Waitr’s sole determination, materially affects the contest or giveaway, Waitr may suspend the contest or giveaway and select potential winners from among all eligible submissions received at the time of suspension. Notice of such action will be posted at https://twitter.com/ WaitrApp. Waitr reserves the right at its sole discretion to disqualify any individual suspected of tampering with the entry process, or the operation of the contest or giveaway; or to be acting in any manner deemed by Waitr to be in violation of the Rules; or to be acting in any manner deemed by Waitr to be unsportsmanlike or disruptive, or with intent to annoy, abuse, threaten or harass any other person. Any fraud or attempt by an participant or any other individual to deliberately undermine the legitimate operation of the contest or giveaway may be a violation of criminal and civil laws and should such an attempt be made, Waitr reserves the right to cooperate in the prosecution of any such individual(s) to pursue all remedies to the fullest extent permitted by law. Sponsor: Waitr, Inc., 4310 Ryan Street, Suite 113, Lake Charles, LA 70605, 877-263-1494. Guidelines for Reviews: Reviews are approved based on the following criteria: **RELEVANCY** Reviewers must have had a firsthand experience with the restaurant using the Waitr app. **ACCEPTABLE CONTENT** Lesson one: We can reject and remove any comment without warning or explanation. We’re not going to as long as you follow our guidelines, but we do reserve that right. As for those guidelines: 

  * No offensive language.
  * Discrimination based on the grounds of race, religion, gender, national origin, age, marital status, sexual orientation or disability will not be tolerated.
  * Referencing illegal activity is not okay.
  * Competing restaurants are not allowed to post negative reviews.  _Violation of this policy will result in permanent removal from our site without a refund._
  * Allegations of health code violations are not acceptable.

**APPROPRIATE** Children under 13 are not allowed to use the site. **NOT ENDORSED** Waitr does not endorse reviews, and they do not represent our views. We also don’t assume liability for the content of any review. **OWNED BY WAITR** We own all reviews exclusively and forever. We have the right to reproduce, modify, translate, transmit and distribute all materials relating to reviews. We are under no obligation to pay you for your reviews. **REMOVABLE** Each review may be removed if requested by one of our users. If you are offended by something on the site [let us know here.](http://waitrapp.com/contact-us)
